"Namu Amida Butsu"
"Namu Amida Butsu" Believe it or not,
the world is filled with strange phenomena
Believe it or not, the world is
filled with strange phenomena
that science has yet to explain.
And when people come
face to face with them,
they are helplessly thrown
into the dark depths of fear.
But there are those who fight every day
to shine a ray of hope
into that chaotic darkness.
People call them...
"Psychics"
..."psychics."
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
I realized that my youth was grey
The root of this irritation is unknown
My brain runs parallel with this emotional train
Struggling adolescence
Don't disturb the subconscious mind
Who's that behind me?
Opposing ideas, distortion
Purge the sorrow
So, do what you can now.
My life
Finally
Break it down!!
(WANT) desire (YOUNG) and sincerity
(BURN) they begin to sprout (1) within my chest
(TRANCE) I won't awaken (CHANCE) but I want to
(STANCE) both sides of the coin
(1) are back-to-back
Accept me as I am
Conflicting freedom and relations
If they can become one
That smile will be
One and only "1"
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
"Mob Psycho 100 "
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
"1st Career Path Survey"
Career path survey?
What? You still haven't filled yours out?
No, I couldn't think of anything.
Well, I plan on going to
a school that studies UFOs.
"Finals Score Ranking by Grade Rank 305/352" Well,
I plan on going to a school that studies UFOs.
"Finals Score Ranking by Grade
Rank 305/352"
I'm gonna go work at a game company.
"Rank 297/352" "Rank 339/350"
"Rank 297/352" "Rank 339/350" I
just wrote down plain ol' office worker.
"Rank 297/352" "Rank 339/350"
"Rank 313/347" I'm a first-year, so
I'm still contemplating my options.
"Rank 313/347"
Yeah...
"Rank 190/350"
"Rank 190/350" But I guess you're
all actually thinking about this.
But I guess you're all
actually thinking about this.
By the way, I heard that Takane-san is
going to apply to Yuzu Pepper High School.
Huh? The Yuzu High?
Yeah, you need at least
a standard score of 65.
It's one of the top three schools
in our prefecture.
"Yuzu Pepper High School" It's one of
the top three schools in our prefecture.
"Yuzu Pepper High School"
Well, she's just...
...clearly in a different league than us.
Wow... Tsubomi-chan's amazing.
What? Seriously?
Yuzu High is affiliated with
a British high school,
"Rank 4/350" Yuzu High is
affiliated with a British high school,
"Rank 4/350"
so we can even study abroad.
Man, studying abroad sounds super fun.
"Progress Toward
Mob's Explosion"
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 7%"
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" Yeah, they totally
made me fill one of these out when I was a student, too.
Yeah, they totally made me fill one of
these out when I was a student, too.
Well, at least you're lucky.
You know where you're going in the future.
Master?
Why, here, of course.
This is your calling! Am I right?
Er, but this is just a part-time job.
No, you never know.
There is a possibility that this
will turn into a reputable agency
with a handful of full-time
employees in the future.
In the future?
"The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen Arataka"s
Spirits and Such Consultation Office" In the future?
"The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen
Arataka's Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen Arataka's Spirits and Such
Consultation Office" Did you plan on opening this consultation office
"The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen
Arataka's Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen Arataka"s Spirits and Such
Consultation Office" ever since you were in middle school, Master Reigen?
Wha--? Of course not.
What kind of middle schooler would?
Then why did you decide on doing this?
Huh?! Why...?
Well, you know... Yeah.
One day, I realized I had
very unique powers...
I'd basically achieved everything
I could at my old job at the time,
so I was looking for a new challenge.
So you did everything you could at your
old job, then opened up this office...
You truly are amazing, Master.
Yeah, pretty much.
I'm done cleaning the bathrooms.
Good.
By the way, you don't need to report
every little thing back to me.
Y-Yes, sir.
It's good to see you, Shigeo-kun.
Oh, hello.
Our client should be here any minute.
Listen up, Serizawa!
Even though I've officially hired you,
you're still a newbie
that's brand spankin' new!
Make sure you watch how
I deal with this client
to learn how this job is done.
Yes, sir! I'll do my best!
But Master Reigen's younger...
I found this at an antiques shop
during one of my travels.
Thinking back on it now,
it feels like it has brought me
nothing but bad luck,
and I haven't been able to sleep.
People have been telling me
I don't look so well lately, either.
Would you mind using
your clairvoyance on it?
"Executing the Exorcism!!” "Option A -- Trial Course"” "A Mere 2,000 yen" "Option B -- Serious Course” "A Mere
5,000 yen" "Option C -- All-Out Course"” "A Mere 12,000 yen" Would you mind using your clairvoyance on it?
"Executing the Exorcism!!” "Option A -- Trial Course"” "A Mere 2,000 yen" "Option B --
Serious Course” "A Mere 5,000 yen" "Option C -- All-Out Course"” "A Mere 12,000 yen"
"Executing the Exorcism!!” "Option A -- Trial Course"” "A Mere 2,000 yen" "Option B -- Serious
Course” "A Mere 5,000 yen" "Option C -- All-Out Course"” "A Mere 12,000 yen" As you wish.
"Executing the Exorcism!!” "Option A -- Trial Course"” "A Mere 2,000 yen" "Option B --
Serious Course” "A Mere 5,000 yen" "Option C -- All-Out Course"” "A Mere 12,000 yen"
May I ask how much you bought this for?
Eighty thousand yen.
Yikes.
From my observations, I don't sense
any spiritual presence from--
Master.
What is it, Mob?
You probably shouldn't
touch that thing anymore.
I wonder if it's called
a deep-seated grudge...
There's a lot of really
bad things swirling in it.
It'll probably get pretty dangerous
if we leave it alone.
Let us exorcise it after all.
Could you wait in
the café upstairs for now?
"Hideaway Café"
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"Hideaway Café" "Spirits and
Such Consultation Office" S-Sure...
"Hideaway Café"
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
I understand your opinion
on this matter, Mob.
Okay...
Well, Serizawa?
How do you feel about this?
Me?
I mean...
I can't imagine it
being anything but a cursed doll.
Serizawa... Why did you just
stand there gawking, then?
Huh?
If I actually didn't notice the curse,
there would've been a huge problem.
I was just testing you to see
if you'd notice my mistake.
Th-Then I...
Well, you're a rookie,
so I'll let this slide.
Do you want a second chance?
Try exorcising it yourself.
Y-Yes, sir.
I did it.
What do you think, Mob?
Serizawa-san is very powerful.
All right! Great job, Serizawa.
Keep up the good work.
Oh, that must've been from the blast.
I-1 broke an 80,000 yen doll...
I-I'm gonna go get some credit somehow!
Hold it!
Don't worry.
"Tuna & Mayonnaise"
I'll take care of it.
Wha... What are you going to do?
Rice Grain Big Bang!
"Rice Grain Big Bang"
"Rice Grain Big Bang" This is one of
Reigen's special attacks, where he unlocks
"Rice Grain Big Bang"
"Rice Grain Big Bang" the true potential
of a rice grain to the fullest extent.
The true potential of
a rice grain to the fullest extent.
H-He fixed it!
At this moment, Serizawa was rocked
to the core by Reigen's limitless abilities,
and he found out just how
big the world truly was.
What's the matter, Shige?
You've barely eaten at all.
I have to turn in my career path survey,
but I'm not sure what to do.
You have almost ten years
before you graduate college,
so why don't you just put down
"office worker" for now?
Oh, dear. You're always too simplistic.
I don't even know what to do
for high school yet.
If you can't think of what you want to do,
"Finals Score Ranking by Grade
Rank 5/347"
"Finals Score Ranking by Grade Rank 5/347" why not try to
find a job where you can use what you already excel at?
"Finals Score Ranking by Grade
Rank 5/347"
"Finals Score Ranking by Grade Rank
5/347" In your case... maybe a magician.
In your case... maybe a magician.
So simplistic...
"1st Career Path Survey"
"1st Career Path Survey" You know, you
can write whatever you want at this point.
You know, you can write
whatever you want at this point.
Dimple.
Your career path can change
all it wants to later.
Nah, I can't do that.
This is for my future, after all.
You just can't lie, can you?
What are you going to do
in the future, Dimple?
You're asking an evil spirit
about his future?
You're naturally ruthless. You know that?
I guess... Sorry.
Hey, hang on a sec.
Didn't I also...
Oh, right. I'd forgotten.
"Body Improvement Club"
Career path, eh?
Well, my family runs a farm,
so once I graduate high school,
"Finals Score Ranking by Grade Rank 343/352" Well, my
family runs a farm, so once I graduate high school,
"Finals Score Ranking by Grade
Rank 343/352"
Rank 343/352" I might be taking over that.
I might be taking over that.
I'm gonna be going to high school.
"Rank 267/352" "Rank 283/352"
"Rank 267/352" "Rank 283/352" Through
a track and field sports recommendation.
"Rank 267/352" "Rank 283/352"
"Rank 267/352" "Rank 283/352" I'm going to
get a job where I can work out my muscles.
I'm going to get a job where
I can work out my muscles.
My parents want me
to become a civil servant,
"Rank 2/350" "Rank 319/352" My
parents want me to become a civil servant,
"Rank 2/350" "Rank 319/352"
but with my grades...
"Rank 2/350" "Rank 319/352" I love animals,
so I've already decided I'm going to be a vet.
I love animals, so I've already
decided I'm going to be a vet.
"Rank 351/352"
"Rank 351/352" Onigawara, you said
you were gonna be a manga artist, right?
Onigawara, you said you were
gonna be a manga artist, right?
Goda, what the hell, man?!
--You said you were gonna go to a co-ed
high school that had a manga club.
--Hey! You can shut up now!
--You said you were gonna go to a co-ed high school that had a manga club.
--The hell're you explainin' all that for?! Read the room, you jerk!
--I guess everyone's got a pretty good idea about their futures already.
Yeah, I figured as much...
But seeing your expression
tells me I'm right.
Mezato-san?
What are you talking about?
The terrorist attack the other day.
Society thinks it was an attack on this town
accompanied by a natural disaster,
but I figured that behind the scenes,
there was a fight for the fate
of the world going on.
You fought an evil organization
and defeated them...
But you also suffered a great loss, too.
That about covers it, huh?
Actually, I was trying to
figure out my career path...
Seriously?! Just look at that thing!
I already know you had
something to do with it!
Some people are starting
to call it a Divine Tree.
Meaning people are worshiping that thing.
You should tell everyone who you are!
That you were the one
who created that Divine Tree!
Is this related to the thing
you mentioned before?
The Psycho Helmet Religion!
You want to connect that
thing with them somehow?
"The Psycho Helmet Religion
New Followers Welcome"
"The Psycho Helmet Religion New Followers
Welcome" You actually get it for once. Exactly!
"The Psycho Helmet Religion
New Followers Welcome"
"The Psycho Helmet Religion New Followers
Welcome" Mob-kun... You're truly amazing!
Mob-kun... You're truly amazing!
I never imagined that one of my classmates
would end up being so divine.
When I look back on my life,
this might be the biggest thing
that's ever happened to it!
Do you know what you're going
to do in the future, Mezato-san?
Huh? Where'd that come from?
"Rank 60/350"
I think... I'm gonna be a photographer.
A journalist. Something like that.
I'm sure there'll be even bigger
things in your life, Mezato-san.
Plenty of them.
Er... I don't think that's
gonna happen again.
It's not all about using fancy words,
or how big something may look.
What else is there?
For me... Like when I joined
the Body Improvement Club.
How is that a huge deal?
It's not that different from what
you're saying, Mezato-san.
I mean... That thing's a broccoli.
Oh, I see. It's just a broccoli...
Uh... How the hell am I
supposed to accept that?!
Then what are you going to do
in the future, Mob-kun?
Well... I can't think of anything.
In the end, I'm glad you're not
the least bit convincing.
I was afraid you'd gained enlightenment
because you're so unpopular.
Without a doubt...
...I am being possessed by an evil spirit.
I've talked to many
psychics up until now,
but no one has been able
to exorcise this evil spirit.
Uh-huh... I see.
In my opinion...
there's definitely something here.
I knew it! I'm glad I hired you!
R-Roaches are terrifying!
Could you, uh... perhaps tell me
what made you think that?
Well, my shoulders are really heavy,
and I experience sleep paralysis.
I brush my teeth all the time
and still managed to get cavities.
The reason I got fired from my part-time job
must also be due to that evil spirit.
I never touched a female coworker's ass.
I was falsely accused.
My hand just happened to brush against
the back of their hand sometimes.
That evil spirit even chased
my girlfriend away!
Oho... You had a girlfriend?
Yes. She was young and a great gal,
but when I told her I was broke,
she suddenly did a 180 on me...
She was like an evil spirit herself.
She even said I was her type.
Oh, and I've been losing
way more hair lately.
It's like someone's ripping
them outta my head.
Right... So about this mountain of garbage...
It's not garbage! It's my legacy!
It's like a barrier, see?
I can sleep soundly as
long as it's around me.
Barrier, you say...
This photo--
Ro--!
That's an old picture.
I was a bit of a rebel back then.
He never had any...
You two... keep listening
to what our client has to say.
I'm going to go grab some
powerful exorcism tools...
Sure...
If no one can get rid of this evil spirit
for me, will my life just be over?
Am I doomed to just repeat these
meaningless days until my death?
My parents died when I was in my 20s,
and my relatives have cut ties with me.
"Shoulders heavy, sleep paralysis, cavities even when he brushes his teeth, fired from job, girlfriend
left, EVIL SPIRIT, garbage" My parents died when I was in my 20s, and my relatives have cut ties with me.
"Shoulders heavy, sleep paralysis, cavities even when he brushes
his teeth, fired from job, girlfriend left, EVIL SPIRIT, garbage"
"Shoulders heavy, sleep paralysis, cavities even when he brushes his teeth, fired
from job, girlfriend left, EVIL SPIRIT, garbage" I have no acquaintances and no job.
I have no acquaintances and no job.
Wait, is my life already over?
I understand exactly how you feel.
When I was confined to my room,
I wondered if that's where I would
spend the rest of my life...
I'm also wondering what's going to happen to me
if I can't decide a career path for myself...
I've been alive 50 years...
I had 50 years...
But all I've got left is this house
that my parents left me.
I have nothing I can truly call my own.
I basically went with the flow
and kept choosing the easy way out.
If only I had chosen
the right path back then...
I guess your life really
does end after one mistake.
Whatever. This is a pain.
--You don't need to try so hard.
--One item at 490 yen.
Two items at 670 yen.
"Mosquito Coils - 30 coils" "Good
Hydrogen Water" "Roach Buster"
"Mosquito Coils - 30 coils” "Good Hydrogen
Water" "Roach Buster" One item at 540 yen.
Let's just do this tomorrow.
I'm sluggish and tired.
Let's just go to bed for the day.
"Fried Chicken Fair"
Thanks.
Evil spirits absolutely hate
clean rooms. Now, we'll...
Wh-What the...?
Hey, hey, hey!
Is it coming from the garbage house?!
You don't need to work so hard, either.
Are they the evil spirit's minions?!
--Don't try so hard. You'll get sick if you work too hard. Just go to bed.
--Seriously, don't work so hard. Let's just go to bed.
Double Hydrogen Water Mist!
"Hydrogen Water Mist"
"Hydrogen Water Mist" This is one of Reigen's special
attacks, where he repels an evil spirit's attack
This is one of Reigen's special attacks,
where he repels an evil spirit's attack
with the hydrogen gas
that's infused in water.
Evil spirits for evil spirits
by evil spirits...
Hey, what are you guys doing?!
Oh, Master. You're back.
Don't give me that!
Look! There's clearly an evil spirit here!
Oh, you're right.
I didn't realize he was being
possessed by one so large.
No, I'm pretty sure...
that's his own living wraith...
Whichever.
My powers are far too strong,
and I may hurt some passersby.
I'm counting on you two.
Evil spirits for evil spirits
by evil spirits...
Evil spirits--
Let's go to bed.
Wow.
I had no idea this place was so huge.
Thank you very much.
Now I think I'll be able to live
the rest of my life in a positive way.
Well, that's great to hear.
But, er... Your roof's in bad shape...
Oh, well, my parents had
the place insured, so it'll be fine.
Whew...
I guess the only thing you can
truly rely on is insurance.
This isn't insurance...
...but please take this.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" "The New Star
of the Spiritual World" ...but please take this.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"The New Star of the Spiritual World"
"Weekly Shonen Ura Sunday"
What's wrong, Serizawa? You feeling sick?
That just hit too close to home.
I'm in the same boat.
I've lived 30 years...
and I've got nothing.
You're not gonna last in this business
if you're affected by every client.
You haven't even reached
the halfway point of your life yet.
If you're regretting everything up until now,
consider yourself lucky for being
able to realize it so early.
Right, Mob?
It hit too close to home for me, too...
Seriously?!
I just haven't made a huge mistake yet,
but that moment may arrive someday.
Thinking about that makes me scared
about which path to choose.
You're seriously thinking all that?
"Prospective Career Path"
"Prospective Career Path" Right... I guess it's about
that time of year when they ask you to pick a career path.
Right... I guess it's about that time of year
when they ask you to pick a career path.
I think you'll be all right, Serizawa-san.
You get to hear stories from
all kinds of people working there,
and you learn a lot.
But I...
"Progress Toward
Mob's Explosion"
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 18%"
So you're choosing to continue
on to high school for now.
In the end, I just couldn't think of anything.
If you're shooting for a public school,
we'll have to do something about
your math and geography scores.
Do your best on your next test, Kageyama.
Huh? Uh, yes, sir.
That's it?
Though... if you have some kind
of goal for your future,
it makes it easier to plan out your life.
There's no need to hurry, but if you
don't find something in your teens,
you may struggle later.
Recently, I started wanting to go
on some relaxing trips on my own.
"Future" "Hope" "Prospects” Recently, I started
wanting to go on some relaxing trips on my own.
"Future" "Hope" "Prospects”
"Future" "Hope" "Prospects” I wish I'd
realized that when I was much younger.
I wish I'd realized that
when I was much younger.
Then again, after seeing
you in that marathon,
I think you'll be okay.
Sir...
I think traveler might
be a great option, too.
"Class 2-1 No. 7 Student Name: Kageyama Shigeo Guardian's Name: Kageyama Nobuhiko" "(1)
What do you plan to do after you graduate" I think traveler might be a great option, too.
"Class 2-1 No. 7 Student Name: Kageyama Shigeo Guardian's Name:
Kageyama Nobuhiko" "(1) What do you plan to do after you graduate”
"Class 2-1 No. 7 Student Name: Kageyama Shigeo Guardian's Name: Kageyama Nobuhiko" "(1) What do
you plan to do after you graduate" I'm honestly a bit concerned at how easily you're influenced.
"Class 2-1 No. 7 Student Name: Kageyama Shigeo Guardian's Name:
Kageyama Nobuhiko" "(1) What do you plan to do after you graduate”
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
There was a blue light shining
There was a blue light shining "Spirits and Such
Consultation Office" I gave it a lot of thought...
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
I gave it a lot of thought...
I'm wide awake this 1:30 AM "Spirits and Such
Consultation Office" I gave it a lot of thought...
I'm wide awake this 1:30 AM
I gave it a lot of thought...
I'm wide awake this 1:30 AM But I don't think my career
path's going to be at Spirits and Such Consultation Office.
But I don't think my career path's going to be
at Spirits and Such Consultation Office.
Just like a sudden bruise out of nowhere But I don't think my
career path's going to be at Spirits and Such Consultation Office.
But I don't think my career path's going to be
at Spirits and Such Consultation Office.
The outline of the pain faintly appears But I don't think my
career path's going to be at Spirits and Such Consultation Office.
The outline of the pain faintly appears
I held on to it as I was losing it
I see.
It's really comfortable here,
and I can talk to you about anything.
This slightly embarrassing new page It's really
comfortable here, and I can talk to you about anything.
It's really comfortable here,
and I can talk to you about anything.
What remained even after I swiped It's really
comfortable here, and I can talk to you about anything.
It's really comfortable here,
and I can talk to you about anything.
Are the smiles of my friends right beside me
But if I get too comfortable here,
Are the smiles of my friends right beside me I think
that my age will be the only thing that changes.
I think that my age will be
the only thing that changes.
I'm sorry, Master Reigen.
I can't promise you that I'll be
working here in the future.
Yes, I want someone to understand... I can't
promise you that I'll be working here in the future.
Yes, I want someone to understand...
This wish that's hidden colorless and invisible
Mob. Of course, I was only kidding.
The breath I was holding deep within my heart
I let it all out at once and return to my senses
Mob. Of course, I was only kidding.
I let it all out at once and return to my senses You'll
eventually find plenty of things you'll want to do.
You'll eventually find plenty
of things you'll want to do.
On days that I'm feeling apathetic it suddenly comes to mind
You'll eventually find plenty of things you'll want to do.
You'll eventually find plenty
of things you'll want to do.
These seasons I spent as if they were a given You'll
eventually find plenty of things you'll want to do.
These seasons I spent as if they were a given
These seasons I spent as if they were a given Remember
when you asked me why I opened up this office?
Remember when you asked me
why I opened up this office?
Even if reality becomes sullied Remember when
you asked me why I opened up this office?
Remember when you asked me
why I opened up this office?
Only the sky we saw together is real Remember
when you asked me why I opened up this office?
Only the sky we saw together is real
Y-Yes...
Only the sky we saw together is real I know
what I said the other day, but the truth is,
I know what I said the
other day, but the truth is,
This is more incomprehensible I know what
I said the other day, but the truth is,
I know what I said the
other day, but the truth is,
Than the grammar on the blackboard I know
what I said the other day, but the truth is,
Than the grammar on the blackboard
I got bored at my old job
If it's going to disappear within 24 hours
and just started this office on a whim.
And just started
this office on a whim.
This flowing story is just too lonely
and just started this office on a whim.
And just started
this office on a whim.
I just can't do it
I just can't do it At first, I figured I'd
get bored after about a year and quit.
At first, I figured I'd get bored
after about a year and quit.
Just like that back hip circle I gave up on At first,
I figured I'd get bored after about a year and quit.
At first, I figured I'd get bored
after about a year and quit.
But I'm not going to... At first, I figured
I'd get bored after about a year and quit.
But I'm not going to...
But that was right around the time...
Give up
Anyway, after some twists
and turns, here we are today.
My present anymore Anyway, after
some twists and turns, here we are today.
Anyway, after some twists
and turns, here we are today.
I adorn my overflowing emotions Anyway, after
some twists and turns, here we are today.
Anyway, after some twists
and turns, here we are today.
And run through my worries and hesitations Anyway,
after some twists and turns, here we are today.
And run through my worries and hesitations
At first, it was just on a whim,
It can't be decided from 0 to 100
It can't be decided from 0 to 100 but I wouldn't be
lying when I say that this is what I want to do now.
But I wouldn't be lying when I say
that this is what I want to do now.
Draw the incomplete future with this hand but I wouldn't
be lying when I say that this is what I want to do now.
But I wouldn't be lying when I say
that this is what I want to do now.
We can't even prove its existence but I wouldn't be
lying when I say that this is what I want to do now.
We can't even prove its existence
What I'm saying is
We can't even prove its existence whatever
you want to do doesn't have to be work.
Whatever you want to do
doesn't have to be work.
But as the world stabs the middle of my chest
whatever you want to do doesn't have to be work.
Whatever you want to do
doesn't have to be work.
It overflows with cobalt blue whatever
you want to do doesn't have to be work.
It overflows with cobalt blue
You should just live however you want to.
True blue...
Master Reigen...
Right!
True blue...
Thank you very much!
English Translator: Michelle Tymon Translation Editor:
Zachary Carlysle Translation Checker: Sriram Gurunathan
Huh? But we're still open for the day...
"Future - Career Paths~" Huh?
But we're still open for the day...
"Future
- Career Paths~"
"Future - Career Paths~"
Is he coming back...?
"Future
- Career Paths~"
Welp...
Guess my time's arrived.
Those who writhe in the shadows
have finally made their move.
Will we be able to stop
this cycle of sadness?
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Il Episode 2:
"Yokai Hunter Amakusa Haruaki Appears!
- The Threat of a Hundred Demons!!~."
Watching /Il in real time
is still a wise decision.
"Yokai Hunter Amakusa Haruaki Appears!
- The Threat of a Hundred Demons!!~" Watching ||| in real time is still a wise decision.
- The Threat of a Hundred Demons!!~"